hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast listeners welcome to the
junkyard love podcast today I'm here
with Matt McGee hello Matt welcome to
the podcast hey Jacob how's it going
it's good man I'm happy to uh I'm happy
to to make this happen I actually last
minute rescheduled on you so I do
appreciate you you working with me on
there man just we're just humans right
just humans doing this podcast thing
absolutely happy to be here yeah
um well so everybody will see from the
title and a little bit of a bio down
below check that out but um for those
who want to know a little bit more in
depth I would love to know kind of your
elevator pitch of who you are what
you're doing what you're here to talk
about uh what what's what's guiding your
life basically basically um who who are
you Matt the hardest question for sure
uh so I mean I guess to boil it down to
the to the to the Bare Bones I am an
educational consultant so I work with uh
family
who are kind of across the board um
whether they're looking for tutoring
whether they're looking to try and get
into college uh whether they're already
in college and they need support sort of
uh developing their course load figuring
out what internships to take um and yeah
so my my essential job is to take
families who are very anxious about uh a
process in an educational system which
is very difficult to navigate and I
alleviate that anxiety and that's kind
of the view from like 30,000 ft
nice yeah excellent excellent yeah
because I imagine it I mean for me I
didn't do much College myself but it's
just such a daunting thing you don't
even know where to start so even just
being able to have someone who goes hey
I I got you let's work through this
together is probably huge for people I
imagine H absolutely and that's the
funny thing right so you know you say
you didn't really go to college I went
to Michigan State which you know for
anybody who's in the sort of college
search knows that's not really like a
competitive school and I sit here in my
industry with a number of other people
who are like you know I went to Harvard
and I have two degrees from Harvard or I
went to Yale and then MIT for grad
school uh and I'm like you know I don't
know I don't know that that's what
people want to work with I think they
they think well that's you know that's
where I want to go so that's a great
thing but what I've come to realize is
that it's just it's it's just a very
anxious time for people they don't they
don't know what they're getting into and
they just want somebody who kind of
understands the system understands what
people are looking for and and and they
just want to guide in that way yeah I
mean makes a ton of sense I would be in
the same boat myself um well I mean
so I guess why do you think that it is
so anxiety written like why is it so
stressful and I guess why is it
stressful we're in 2024 right now what's
different today than it was maybe 10 20
years
ago that's a really good question um I
don't even think we could probably cover
that in the hour that we have today um
you need yeah because by the time this
conversation finishes AI or chat GPT has
released another new version that
changes yeah exactly um and it's only
gotten it's only just gotten more
complex through the pandemic right I
mean you know when
when when we were in high school the
formula was pretty simple get good
grades get a decent score on the SAT you
write a personal statement that you know
isn't terrible um and then you kind of
know your r of schools that you can
apply to um but it it really changed
during the pandemic there were a number
of things that that happened one they
sort of went test optional so anybody
who had sort of you didn't have to have
an SAT score right normally you'd have
to say I need like a 1500 or 1550 to
even have a shot at Harvard then they
said well you don't need that and so
everyone said well maybe I have a shot
at Harvard so their application numbers
and this wasn't just obviously at
Harvard it was across the board you'd
see application numbers that were like
12,000 applications all of a sudden in
one year shot up to like 30,000
applications wow so it just became a
much more competitive process and I
think when you couple that with um
Rising prices where you're looking you
know when we were when we were doing
this process again a state school was
like5 $10,000 the the the high-end
schools were $40,000 now you're looking
at USC and it's $100,000 a year to go
there right um You got the issues with
FAFSA and people not knowing how to fill
out about that form and so it's just
becoming it's becoming more and more
complicated and there is very there is
very little explanation as to why right
it's a very opaque process you don't
really come across people who work in
admissions right when was the last time
you were at a party and you talk to
somebody who was like oh yeah I'm a
Stanford admissions officer or I'm an
admissions officer at any you don't meet
these people and so you go like what is
what is the criteria to get in what are
the standards that you're looking for
and people don't know and so you have
these students who are hyper qualified
you're talking about people who have you
know a 4.0 GPA in the most difficult
classes that you could imagine uh with
you know they they're part of this club
and they're part of that club and
they're leaders and they built their
their uh nonprofit organization and they
apply to all these schools and they
don't get in and they're going why I
don't you I I don't know why um and I
think when you start to add all these
questions on top of each other people
just start to go I I have no idea I
can't figure it out and that makes
people very anxious especially when you
couple it with the fact that it's a huge
part of your life right if you go to
this school it's going to open up these
opportunities if you go to that school
it's going to open up those
opportunities if you don't go to school
that's a huge decision and then you boil
in social media to the equation where
you see these people who are going I did
all these things and that's how I got
into Harvard and I did all these things
that's how I got into Stanford and you
have these kids you know Doom scrolling
through Instagram going I got to get
into Harvard I got to get into Stanford
because I want this job I want that job
and it just it's like a positive
feedback loop of anxiety and stress and
destruction and whatnot and so here I am
trying to go let's take a step back
let's let's let's take some of the
stress and the anxiety off this and and
figure out how we can best move forward
and kind of address the mental health
aspect as well as the academic aspect
yeah I feel like you you serve a a great
role of a med like H let's just relax
you know come calm down we could figure
this out and then and then you guide
them so so what is the you know that
person who does have you know they were
leaders and they were you know the the
senior class president and they were
maybe Val victorium they've got four 4.0
those people who who do think that they
have a good chance and then they end up
they're not able to get in or whatever
so what is
their when when they come to you curious
about what to get in or or or how to get
in I I mean what is your answer for that
when they have trouble getting in so you
said all these people we have more and
more applications and then we have more
and more people who are obviously very
much qualified I mean how are we
deciphering between these people who are
not qualified and are qualified how are
the how are the big schools even making
these decisions
nowadays that's another great question
uh it it is an extremely opaque process
because nobody has insight into it I
mean it essentially comes down to I
think a lot of people don't know what
the admissions process looks like right
so you're going to submit an application
that has all the things on it and if if
I'm your admissions officer right you're
in the kind of region that I've been
assigned to I'm GNA get your application
I'm GNA look at it and I'm GNA
go I'm gonna say one of three things I'm
gonna either say uh you know Jacob is
great and I think he'll do great in the
next round and we'll we're definitely
going to advance him uh there's going to
be a I think Jacob could meet you know
the criteria to get in and I'm gonna I'm
gonna advocate for him in the next round
and then there's uh you know Jacob
doesn't quite meet the requirements here
we don't think he's going to fit in here
and then you know we'll move you and you
won't really move on to the next round
and they have a number of scoring
systems generally they'll kind of rate
you between like a one and a six uh for
kind of putting you in that criteria but
then after the admissions officer after
I've looked at that and said hey I'm
going to move you to the next round now
I'm going to sit in a committee with all
the admissions officers who did that
from the first round and I'm going to
say I've got Jacob and he is excellent
candidate or I've got Jacob and his
grades aren't great his SAT score is
really good but I think he's really
great for X Y and Z and I think he'll
really you know Vibe with the campus
life and I think we should really give
him a shake and everybody in the
committee is going to have those
students of their own and they're all
going to ask each other questions you
know what is it about Jacob's
temperament that you really think is
going to fit in with this campus Jacob
said this in his essay and I'm not
entirely sure that that fits with our
values what makes you think that it does
right and so it's going to become a
conversation like that and I think what
people fail to realize is they treat it
like they treat it in a more um
objective way than it is it's a very
subjective process right when you think
about the kind of like debate that I'm
describing uh the kind of uh
philosophical discussion that's going on
there whereas I think people tend to
look at it as I got a 4.0 and I got a
1600 which means that inherently I am a
higher qualified candidate than the kid
who got a three and a
and that's not exactly what it is right
so there's other factors that they're
going in there so you'll have situations
in which the kid with the four point and
the 1600 doesn't get into the the number
one rank school but he gets into the
three and four rank school and the kid
with the 38 GPA and the 1500 he gets
into the top school but he doesn't get
into the third and the fourth school why
could be something that they wrote about
in their essay that reflected the values
could be that one of them was doing a
project uh you know outside of school
and extracurricular that really excited
the admissions officer could be that
they were just trying to fill some sort
of a quota and get uh you know somebody
from a different part of the country or
a different part of the world to fit in
there so there's a million things that
go into these decisions and we don't see
those and so I think for these kids
they're going like why why wasn't I
chosen you know what's wrong with me so
so my kind of My Philosophy is look
let's get narrow let's be specific about
who we are who are you what are you
interested in what do you want to major
in what do you love to do and go pursue
those things be proactive be interesting
be a three-dimensional student don't
just focus on you know academics and
test scores because there's so much to
that and then let's not be committed to
Harvard or Stanford or the University of
Chicago because if you are a good enough
student you are that excellent High
achiever we're going to apply to 10 15
maybe 20 schools and the ones who are
right for you will come find you at that
point okay so we're here in 2024 again
what are the benefits of the more Ivy
leak schools I mean seems pretty obvious
like we we've all grown up and we know
these big names you know everybody knows
the obvious of course the connections
and the education that you get these
places is going to be next level but
here in 2024 what are the benefits of
really actually wanting to get into one
of these Ivy League schools and you know
are the the second third fourth tier are
they so bad you know are they they
equally as good
too uh you know I'm I'm biting my tongue
as I say this but I'm going to share
this story I was on a call with uh an
admissions officer and a
um guy who worked in the finance office
at a university that costs between
$90,000 and $100,000 a year to go to not
ivy league not Ivy plus but kind of in
that next level there and uh one of the
questions that was posed to this guy uh
or I was suppos to both of them was um
you know your University costs $100,000
there is another University down the
street offering the same degree program
for $115,000 the the state school
essentially he said you know can you can
you pitch me on why you're University
you know what the
$85,000 difference is there and there
was about a 5-second
pause and then they
said we're going to decline to answer
that
question and it was a very telling
response I thought in so far this guy
basically said um or I took it to mean
and and I think this is a a legitimate
interpretation I took it to mean um we
we can charge that price tag because we
have the value you know it's like a
luxury item right you know uh Hugo Boss
can charge more than you know the brand
or the non-brand name just because they
have the name on there is that to say
that there's no benefit to going to
Harvard or you know an IV leak school no
I mean you look at um I'm gonna I'm
gonna fumble the numbers in front of me
but there is there is a significantly
higher percentage of senators uh
Representatives people in federal
government who went to an ivy Le School
than those who didn't um and so what the
the large or like the top universities
are able to offer you in terms of uh
specialization opportunity uh smaller
class size in a lot of situations you
are able to get a lot of opportunity
there that being said whether you go to
Harvard or Penn or Duke or Stanford
seems to make a little bit less
difference in that you're still going to
get those opportunities at the same time
State schools uh smaller universities
these are great options for people you
can still get a lot done a school like
Michigan State it's not well known for
its academics but it's one of the top
research institutions in the country so
for the right person it's a great place
to go uh and and so so yes there is a
lot of benefit to that but the idea of
like marrying yourself or trying to get
that because you know for the status or
whatnot I think people are maybe going
in the wrong direction there right yeah
yeah it might be evolving I do kind of I
weirdly kind of like that answer that
answer they gave it's partially gangster
a little bit the ball the the thought I
had was the balls the balls say that of
just you know what we charge this
because we can yeah yeah that that's
that's pretty crazy um okay uh we've got
I've got a lot of notes that I want to
cover but um something that was that's
kind of just Whispering at me that I
want to bring up here is H we we talked
on the phone as well um we talked about
like you know students entering into
this world uh with neurode Divergence um
we talked about I mean you've already
mentioned mental health and having
confidence and all the anxieties that
come with this um I guess I kind of want
to know
like I'm not close to that I'm not close
you know as someone who is who is you're
a mentor you you talk to these people
who are coming out of high school you
know they're around the ages of 17 18 19
whatever it is I imagine
um what does that look like why is there
anxiousness um what is
the what's the mental health view of of
all this like is is this another thing
that's different than 10 to 20 years ago
does it look way different is are you
experiencing things that you never
thought you would when you first started
I know that's so many questions packed
into one M but if you can find an answer
it's a lot there but I know that's
that's that's good
um you know I'm a straight white guy
that grew up in the like '90s and early
2000s so like mental health is not ever
anything that I thought would be on my
radar you know what I mean yeah like I
feel like guys like you and me were just
like yeah you know we're here like you
know this is just like I just showed up
and like life was pretty good um so
mental health yeah it never really it
never
really crossed my mind at all but I
think you know since then we've had the
Advent of social media like I spoke
about and that's like you know we all I
guess we all participate in social media
but I think we're also aware of the kind
of like mental health disaster F that it
creates uh especially for young people
who are like comparing themselves to
each other and I think one of the
reasons why you get this highly
competitive admissions process that
wasn't so competitive before
um but I I would say mental health
aspect I think that's one of the chief
aspects that I operate from in what you
know if somebody came to me and said so
you know there's a million College
counselors out there there's a million
uh tutoring companies out there what
what sets you like why I why should I
hire you I would I would go well
look you know there's a number of people
who are going to tell you uh you know
I'll get you a 4.0 GPA or there's a
number of people who tell you you know
I'll get you into an IV League school
for me that's not really my Approach my
Approach is we're going to maximize your
opportunity to get to where you want to
go whether that's talking about like
improving your grades whether that's
talking about getting into the best
school you can get into But ultimately
I'm going to do it and I'm going to keep
you in a place where you don't hate your
while you do do it um so we specifically
have a program that is like a tutoring
program and we partner with other
College counselors so so students who
aren't using me for for College
counseling they will come to us for
tutoring because you got to keep your
grades up right and and and when you
think about what you're going through
now for me applying to college was like
I'm going to look at a couple schools
I'm going to download some applications
write a personal statement I talk to my
history teacher he wrote me a letter of
recommendation now these kids are
starting nonprofits they're doing
research opportunities during the summer
um I had a student who discovered a a
species of fish I had another student
who started a um who started a a
scrunchie business for her volleyball
team when they like went to the state
championship uh in addition to the fact
that they are taking all these APS and
they are doing a ton of test prep right
so like it's a much more significant
workload now so one of the things that
our two ing does is that we like we we
we specifically hire people who are
highly charismatic highly relatable
young individuals who can not only tutor
you in calculus or you know uh AP Bio
but also be somebody Who You're not
responsible to be somebody who a 17 18
yearold kid can just be
like okay like how's it going man and
they're like it's good like you ready to
do some C yeah you know like let's let's
let's crush this let's get this out of
the way like how are you doing you know
um and so to have somebody who can kind
of walk both sides of that where they're
not just your teacher they're not just
somebody who's like trying to you know
be another academic Force but somebody
who's just your your your buddy somebody
who's your boy somebody who can yeah
somebody who can kind of let you breathe
um because these kids are like spinning
themselves crazy trying to trying to do
something that is it's not impossible
but it's it's it's very very difficult
um yeah I imagine the pressure to you
know you see people on Tik Tok or
whatever you're scrolling and you're
like okay well this person's 16 and they
already have this successful business
and so uh I need to now dedicate my life
to starting my own business so I can get
into this school you know I'm sure it is
very stressful for them to think like I
don't have a chance unless I you know
start my own scrunchie business or or
discover a new species like that's just
that's insane I mean I imagine those
those people would have a a higher you
know a higher chance a higher
opportunity because they've done those
impressive things but um yeah yeah that
that that's pretty cool you know I I
think back to me when I was um right
after high school I went to my I went to
um I'm from Washington State originally
there's a community college called Lower
Columbia College and I just I went there
because I just didn't know I was like I
don't really have any plans for what I'm
doing in my life and I don't really have
anybody to tell me what or not to do or
to do so I just started going there and
man I remember it would have been so
great to have someone uh like a mentor
or a tutor to help be my buddy cuz I
felt so confused and I felt like
everybody who I went to like they didn't
have time to help me they just had so
many other things going on just being
able to have a conversation with someone
who was down to Earth but also not you
know too shirt and tie you know you're
17 18 years old you want to connect with
someone you know so that's that's
probably huge do do you find that uh
it's very disarming once people meet you
like you you probably I imagine within
the first meeting you probably relieve a
lot of anxiety huh the amount of the
amount of first meetings that I have
been on where someone
cries the percentage is like
disproportionately High um I've even had
Parents call me it's it's funny like the
breadth of my job because it will go at
times where I'm having a very kind of
astute conversation about uh major
choice and school choice and then I'll
get a call from a parent who's just like
you know my kid's got this dog and he's
not you know taking he's not taking care
of it and I just don't know what else I
can do because he's not doing the work
right and they're they're breaking down
so I'm dealing with all that type of
stuff um but yeah it is it is and that's
that's one of the rewarding Parts about
the job is that people you can almost
see them immediately go
like like yeah oh okay because they come
with like a million questions that any
lay person would have excuse me and so
for me it's easy to go like oh yeah
that's a yes that's a no that's you know
X Y and Z that's a b and c and we'll
talk about the other question you have
and they go like oh that's like 80% of
the questions that I had in in five
minutes um but yeah it's so it's so true
and there's so many there's so many
students especially male students who at
17 18 right like men are behind at 17
and 18 girls are f are maturing so much
faster than we are so you know guys are
looking at like speak for yourself here
speak for yourself just kidding
um you know they're looking at these
girls going like yeah like you said
they're they're founding two companies
and they're you know they're
volunteering and I'm over here like
trying to beat the next level on Call of
Duty and I can't do that uh and so it
like yeah it creates this like trying to
catch up and just to have somebody say
like yeah this is normal this is where
you should be somebody to say that
Community College is a totally
acceptable if not highly intelligent
decision to make if you don't
necessarily know where you're going to
go I know College counselors who will
push people to for your universities
because you know they're able to charge
money for the hourly that goes into that
application where I'm like if you don't
know what you want to do go to a
two-year University you're going to save
50 Grand a
year and you're probably going to come
out more mature and in the end give
yourself a better shot at a better
college and ultimately a better career
better understanding of yourself you'll
have the time to figure it out because
you won't be in this you know Cutthroat
environment where you're comparing
yourself to to everybody else you know
right right yeah how much how much would
you say the the journey into just
entering the world of college you know
we turn 18 and we have these we've just
done the whole thing for 12 years we
followed the carrot on the stick and now
it's time to go out into the big world
you know I oh I mean
what what level of this is is um
I mean what do I want to
say so so like when we're ready for I
mean I mean how much how much are you
helping people like start their own
Heroes journey into themselves like not
even just College I feel like you
probably show up as some sort of it
sounds like you're basically a counselor
in a lot of ways too right like a you
know maybe not necessar therapist but
like friend extended for sure you know
these people are starting those life
it's a big deal you know yeah absolutely
and then you know and like I said there
is a reason why in The Tuning program we
specifically aim for like young
charismatic people who know the journey
that these kids are going under because
it is like highly relatable and there is
there is science approve you will talk
to teachers that like the learning
process accelerates dramatically when
the student feels comfortable with the
person who is offering that information
so I might have like some old like you
said suit and tii teacher who's teaching
me Cal or or whatever it is and I'm
going like uh you know I'm not getting
any of this I don't feel free to fail I
don't feel free to ask questions but
then you put me in the room with the
like 25-year-old who gets it who is who
is cool who's relating to me who's like
telling you know and then all a sudden I
have the freedom to fail I have the
freedom to ask these questions I have
the freedom to look stupid because I'm
building a relationship so many of my
students because I'm a relatively young
guy uh that I work with you know there
are students who I'll start with them
when they're 16 but when I'm done with
them they're they're 22 23 years old and
we've gone from you know our
relationship Evol in that time from you
know I'm more of a teacher at 16 but by
the time they're in college it's much
more of a situation you know it's much
more of a friendship right you know and
they're telling me things about like
what they did last night that they're
not telling their parents and I'm like
yeah you know like that's that's normal
that's to be expected that's where
that's where things should be but yeah
there's also a degree of there is a
degree of therapy like I said you know
how many people are crying on some of
these initial calls uh is that
ultimately yeah these people are dealing
with like I said earlier they're dealing
with anxiety and they just want that
they just want that relieved they want
they want somebody who can who can guide
them and lead them and let them know
it's going to be okay
because it's a big time it's a big
transition you're still a teenager so
your hormones are still raging like all
that's happening um and and like you
said people are people are too busy to
help a lot of the time where they're
kind of like ah you know um
um and so it comes back to just wanting
to give them that moment where they can
like they can take a breath for a second
they can relax they can know that
they're they're taken care of right yeah
that's huge man just being able to hold
space for someone to just you know blah
out that they don't really know exactly
what they're doing but they need help
you know that's that's that's pretty
huge um me I okay so I want to ask you
say I'm say I am raising you know I I've
got a kid and you know you know they're
in their teens and they're they're
approaching high school maybe they're
maybe they're turning 15 16 somewhere
around there and you know they're
starting to think about college we're
starting to talk about college they
don't really know where they want to go
um maybe they have some certain
interests that we want to buckle down on
and and I just I need to know what do
they need to start doing you know if if
I was their parent and and I reached out
to you guys what what does that look
like even just one little foot in the
door of hey we don't know much about
college we don't have any decisions made
yet but we need your help what does that
conversation usually look like yeah for
sure uh so it can look like a number of
things depending on how how many
questions they already have answered you
know some people come and they're like
you know my kid loves math and you know
he's really into robots and he's already
doing this robot competition and you
know he's in BattleBots 2024 and that
then I kind of go like great we have a
huge part of what we need and let's run
with that but to kind of answer that
question question from what I'll say I
mean for lack of a better term the
lowest common denominator not in that
not in quality but in terms of having
the least amount of questions answered
um that starts with what are we
interested in what has your child been
interested in um it's a question about
you know where is your where where is
your ability to pay for college um you
know what is the kind of schedule like
all of these questions and then we start
to get into uh
it it all comes down to you know what is
this kid interested in what are they
passionate about do they have those
things because once we've start to
build their interests their passions
what they care about then we can really
start to kind of like move forward in a
healthy way if you're interested in
politics right then having um you know
making sure that we're taking apus
history making sure that we're taking
honors history and honors English class
making sure that we're getting into
writing classes that's going to be
important and it's also going to be
something that the student enjoys right
if you come to me and you're like I love
politics and government I'm not going to
tell you why you have to take AP
Calculus uh you know that might
ultimately be where you go if you want
to be a really high achieving student
but it's going to be about kind of like
pushing into your interests and making
sure that you're taken care of there
from there we'll start to talk about all
right so what are they doing the Summers
you know are they going away to Camp are
they big into sports
what's going on there so how can we now
take this interest let's say government
politics and how can we start to build a
list of extracurricular or um you know
like uh activities to create to create
what's eventually going to look like on
your resume as a degree of proactivity
and a degree of uh intellectual
curiosity right so if you're seeking out
an internship with a local city
councilmen or you're uh constantly
submitting op EDS to the local paper
about some local election right and and
you start to take those interests and
you turn them
into very specific accomplishments that
not everybody has right if you just take
a 16-year-old or a 15-year-old they're
going to say I'm interested in politics
I read the news I do what I have to do
in class maybe I pick up a book and I
read it but they're not going to have
the direction and the follow through to
kind of go and say how can I get
published right and so that's where my
job is to kind of go and say how can I
sort of Channel your talents how can I
challenge your interest and your
passions into into these more concrete
achievable and uh measurable things that
would look really good on a
resume yeah excellent amazing okay um
man okay I want to ask you one more time
so when when we first talked neurode
Divergence was a thing that was
specifically mentioned um I would love
to you know I'm not sure that I can form
a specific question around that but I
would love to um just loudly kind of
note it and put a question mark next to
it and I guess just kind of ask you to
expand on that for me um like what I
guess you know kind of what does that
mean and how does what does it mean for
you know our modern young people growing
up and uh how does it affect you know
what you do in in our thoughts about
education sure I I love that just neurod
Divergent with a question mark next to
it please yeah so um
so neurod Divergent I mean is a
term that sort of broadly
encompasses uh and I'm I'm I'm likely to
put my foot in my mouth here so I
apologize to anybody if this is not the
exact phrasing that it is uh is to say
that that that someone's someone whose
brain processes information differently
than what we would consider the typical
way of processing information that gets
to be pretty muddy because you go like
what is the typical way of processing
information we all do it differently
like that's what personality is uh but
to I guess to put it in a more
um digestible bit you would consider
somebody who is autistic to be neurode
Divergent you would also consider
somebody who has ADHD to be
neurodivergent dyslexia counts as a
neurod Divergence um people with
physical disabilities I don't believe
are always neurode Divergent but
somebody with Down Syndrome would be
neurode Divergent so it's kind of a a a
nebulous thing there um and we've seen
an increase with it uh over the past
decade I'll say and I think that's
probably a combination of uh one more
exposure and more you know more
awareness surrounding it and then two
uh the decrease of attention spans
related you know going back to social
media and technology and the way that
you know we do that um just kind of talk
about how I work with it uh it it is a
very underserved space um in fact when I
was just getting started I was working
as a private tutor uh with no training
in special education or neurod
Divergence or anything like that and I
was working for a very bougie company
that was charging a lot of money for
tutoring and they sent me two kids and I
said okay great yeah that sounds great
and they said uh cool we'll get you
started and then when I had the
conversations with the parents
the one parent was like you know yes so
we started this home school because my
child is autistic and I spoke to the
next one and they were like yeah so we
had to pull my child out of school
because uh she has such severe anxiety
that she often cannot speak or will not
speak oh wow I was
like yeah and I was also like well I'm
not qualified yeah what do I do about
that why am why would you give me these
things um but ultimately I kind of came
to the conclusion that if they gave them
to me it was because they felt I was the
best person for these you know there it
wasn't though as though there was some
special educator out there who they were
like no let's not give it to him so I I
took on the
cases you paused on my end Matt I'm not
sure if you can hear me I I'm not sure
if it was your end or mine well that's
fine hey we're back on it looks like
it's working good I think we can uh we
can carry on so uh we Matt we were in
the middle of um neuro divergency so you
had someone uh you had two people that
came up one had extreme anxiety someone
had um was it autism that they had
or uh yes one student was autistic the
other student was not but she had um
like I said extreme anxiety to the point
where she couldn't speak um and through
the process I just realized how
underserved these people were that here
they were showing out all this money
expecting this like special educator and
they got me who you know I was I was
down to figure it out and take the time
but like I said you know I was
successful in one case I wasn't as
successful in the other case uh and that
kind of led me down the road of you know
so what do these what do these students
do after they after they finish up after
they finish High School um and
ultimately I realize that a lot of these
families they think that college is not
an option they think that it's not
possible or that you know it's just it's
not feasible for them uh and so I
thought that's crazy because given what
we do you know given what I'm talking
about with trying to find the passions
and the interests in schools wanting to
build a diverse student body you know a
lot of these students in both of these
cases I had you know the the the
autistic student who I was talking about
was hyper interested in um politics and
economics and the other student was
hyper interested uh in art right to the
point where they had an understanding of
this at at 15 16 you know the girl was
like 11 or 12 uh that I don't think I
would be able to have insight into in
years of practice um and so I started to
kind of say like why is this I mean we
could take these people we they they
could go to a top college um and I work
with students who have ADHD who are who
are at you know UC Berkeley or other top
universities and you go there is a there
is a program for students who have
disabilities or students who have a
neurod Divergence you know to be
supported uh and so that's just kind of
one of the things that I have sort of
built is is trying to work with these
students who have different
circumstances to help you know make sure
that they can have the education that
they can have but that they don't always
feel that they or they don't always know
that they can have it if that makes
sense yeah yeah I mean that must be huge
to even be able to offer them and and
tell them like yeah you totally have a
chance like it's just probably sometimes
a huge uh sigh of relief on their end
and their parents end to even see like
you said that it is an option you know
because I I think that especially young
people when we're different when we're
when we you know we can tell we don't
think or act or you know exist the same
way as quote unquote everybody else um
it could kind of you know make us seem
like our our future is already written
in in a sort of way but you know
actually as it turns out I like the um I
don't know if you ever heard I think it
was Alan Watts said if you judge a fish
by his ability to climb a tree he will
live his entire life thinking that he is
stupid or some something along those
lines um but yeah I mean yeah that's so
cool I imagine you probably find those
people like cool what are your skills
cool this college or this this
opportunity is perfect for those
skills that's exactly what it is and so
often they do have these heightened
skills where they you know a a lot of
times uh they latch on to an idea that
they that they love and they have the
attention span and the inclination to
explore that way further than you know
somebody who is quote unquote
neurotypical if you will um and and the
other piece of that too is that a lot of
them go like well I have this thing that
I've always been ashamed of because
you're you know again you're 16 17 18 so
you haven't yet come to that place of
celebrating your differences sure and
and so you know it's also coaching to be
like no you have this thing that sets
you apart and I know you don't see it
now because that's not the way that kids
are but this is going to be this is
going to be a huge a huge thing that
it's going to be something that you can
celebrate it's going to be something
that makes you stand out it's going to
make you know it's going to be um a
distinc ofier which you which is going
to be beneficial in the long run and and
and getting them to kind of celebrate
that in their applications so that they
can they can again stand out because
when you're competing against like
30,000 people you need to stand out in
some sort of
way yeah okay well so so what is your Le
let's queue in a little bit more on what
you just said um standing out you know
everybody has their individual
characteristics everybody has their
their thing that if they you know I'm
sure you help it help bring it out of
them how important is it for people
looking into colleges to stand out and
what I guess what does it mean to stand
out if you're looking at a top
university like if you're looking at
like the top of the top it is it is not
only important it's it's completely
vital to stand out um I would also say
that if you're applying to the kind of
like that second level of University and
you really want to get to that level
again it's very important to stand out
if you're and you're going you know I
want to go to a large state school that
maybe isn't that competitive my scores
are pretty good but you know I'm going
because I want to be part of a big
student body or I want to be um you know
I want to be in a successful sports
program whatever it is you probably
don't need to stand out as much your you
know test scores and your grades will
kind of take care of that for you but
standing out
comes comes in a number of ways
uh standing out sort of sort of is
college applications are ultimately a
story right you're telling a story a lot
of times I operate as like a PR Guy
where I'm like this is you know this is
who Jacob is right and we put it we put
it to him that way um but standing out
can have you know a number of a number
of ways of looking at it in that like
you know the girl to take the example of
the girl with the the scrunchies right
she built that business uh the
volleyball team the girls volleyball
team was going to be really good every
everybody knew they were going to be
really good so she says okay I have this
great idea I'm going to build I'm going
to create these scrunchies right the
like things that girls tie their hair up
with she goes I'm gonna get these
scrunchies we're gonna have like
individualized scrunchies for each one
of the girls on the team and then we're
gonna sell them to the town and you can
buy your favorite player scrunchies
right because the town is super excited
right and she's she's this smart young
affable outgoing girl she's got this
great idea and she starts to get because
it's like you know it's like a couple
thousand it's not like crazy investment
but it's a couple thousand dollars to
get these things like screen printed and
whatnot so she has this great idea she
gets some investment from the people in
the town she has this you know it's
going to be great it's going to blow up
and it flops like no one buys these
scrunchies basically the girls on the
the girls on the team and their families
bought them but nobody bought them
seemed like a great idea it did it
sounds like a great idea right and she
was everyone was excited it fails and so
then this is this is to this day I use
this example anybody who hears me on
another podcast has probably heard this
example is that she opens up her essay
and mind you this girl is going into
business she wants to be a business
major she opens up her essay with the
first time I declared bankruptcy I was
16 years old
wow and you go that makes you stand out
because one it's funny and two it's the
embracing of failure right to go I
failed epically and I'm not going to
hide it I'm not going to I tried
something I tried I failed and you know
what I'm back up and I'm going to move
on to the next thing um so that's one
way you can stand out right the other
way is you know I'll go back to the
example of the kid who discovered the
species of fish how many other people
can say that they have done that um and
so again he was hyper interested in
Wildlife so he spent a lot of his time
in parks and when he did find those fish
I was the one who encouraged him hey
let's get in touch with the local bi uh
the local biologists to kind of like do
some research around this and take it a
little further um we had another student
who wanted to go to MIT the kid did not
really have the grades for Mi uh but he
and and this was like 10 years ago maybe
he had developed a primitive AI system
that helped with organization somehow
like organizing data basically and he
had implemented it at his school library
so that kidss were able to um kids were
able to kind of like Search for the book
that they wanted to but they could also
search for other books that would be
useful to them based on their search
query and we took that and we went to
his local library and we had them
implement it right so you see that on an
application and all of a sudden the the
admissions officer leans forward and
goes like oh this person's thinking
outside the box he got into MIT right
and so it's it's that type of stuff
where you really need to in order to
stand out you need to take your
interests and pursue
them to the point where the opportunity
shows up right it's kind of where like
luck meets hard work and then you know
when that moment happens we've got to
talk about it um because that's how you
stand out because I can tell you what
there's 20,000 high schools in the US
which means there's 20,000
valedictorians and they all have 4.0 GPA
and great test scores and I can tell you
that there's less than 20,000 spots at
all of the Ivy League schools total yeah
so you've got to in some way Stand Out
show your proactivity show your
intellectual curiosity show that you're
you know you're not you're not afraid of
failure uh and show that you're you're a
person who does more than grades in
school and and and piano lessons right
right yeah I'll bet that you end up you
know meeting with people and helping
them pull helping pull that part out of
them you know because I I imagine more
people than they think have something
that's pretty impressive or something
that they know quite a bit about that
they think is just like well yeah
whatever of course I know all about this
fish I like fish and you're like dude
not everybody knows about fish like you
actually have something here you
know that's exactly right I mean even
with the example of fish he was talking
about terms there's like you know a type
of fish that swims to the ocean and a
type of fish that doesn't swim to the
ocean and he's going like yeah they're
these like diandrus fish that they they
go to the ocean and these other ones
they don't do that so they must be
another species and I'm going like I
don't know what you're saying but like
you know this is all this is all really
good stuff like we got to use this um
yeah and so yeah that's that's exactly
what it is and trying to trying to to
pull that out of you because when you're
17 you don't always necessarily know
where you want to go and I think you
know what the question was when I had a
guidance counselor they were sort of
like so what would you do if you didn't
have to worry about money right yeah and
then like if you said I would just like
you know hang out with my car and work
on my car then you were supposed to be a
mechanic and if you were uh you know if
you said I wanted to you know write in
my journal then you were supposed to go
be a writer but to me that's like a you
know that's a that's a question for one
person working with like 150 people but
to really yeah get to know someone and
and allow them to open up to you is is a
whole different ball game yeah yeah I
mean yeah I love all those examples I
feel like that really for me personally
that makes me realize how important you
guys are as mentors and tutors and in in
the role that you serve um being able to
help people kind of figured out I mean
ju something that my mind keeps wanting
to compare it to I've been updating my
resume recently and it's one of those
things where it's you know like I have
accomplished a lot of things but I don't
really know if they're important to
mention or not and then I'll see you
know I'm looking at applications or
looking at you know different gigs or
whatever it is and Linkedin will suggest
certain key terms or keywords or
whatever and I'm like oh I have all
those I didn't realize it was important
to mention on my my resume but if
that'll help me be seen like cool I'll
throw it on there it's completely true I
have that skill I just didn't know know
to include it so yeah I mean it's got to
be so useful for people to meet y'all
and realize that they you know have a
lot of spinning plates and they could
just kind of consolidate them into you
know a narrative to present like here
here's who I am and here's why it's
important to take a look at me well and
that goes back it's so interesting that
you say that about the resume and like
you know having things
that that you didn't necessarily know
were useful because that goes back with
the to the the opaque process the the
opak andess opacity of the process which
is sure I have all these things I know
what I do I know what I like but what do
I
include right and so you you know like I
said we're our job is to kind of be the
pr person to tell the story because
ultimately they don't necessarily care
about every little thing that you did
they don't care about your one year on
JV lacrosse if they're interviewing you
or thinking about you from the the uh
perspective of are we going to let them
into our exclusive bioengineering major
they want to know about the things that
you did there maybe they want to know
about a few other things so they can
gauge your your your proactivity in your
work ethic But ultimately it's it's
those type of things but you know in
terms of figuring out what should I put
on there and what shouldn't I put on
there whether it's a job search or a
college application or a high school
application whatever it is it's
important to have people know that and I
feel like they don't you don't
necessarily know what the person on the
other side of the table wants yeah I
wouldn't have any idea you know now and
especially back then but now I still
don't I'm I'm 33 years old almost I have
no idea so yeah right it's some and or
and it's possible that it's just like AI
right going uh you know Jacob had you
know writer four times on his bio
interviewer or two times right so yeah
we can see him or we can't see him
because of that you go yeah what am I
supposed to do yeah yeah yeah um okay
well so so from what you've seen how
much I mean you mentioned AI I I I
briefly brought it up earlier um I do
kind of want to I want to that might be
another one that I put a question mark
next to for you um H how has it changed
their process you know I think you've
already helped me realize that it's you
know like a a room full of people who
are you know real actual people who are
reading these things and having
conversations about who to let in and
whatnot you know I'm not even sure if I
fully comprehended that but how nowadays
um comprehended that until now until you
explained it but nowadays the um you
know technology keeps on moving and
grooving doesn't it chat GPT still still
keeps improving I'm I'm sure that's not
only changing education and Chang in
high school college and everything but
how is our advancements in technology
specifically changing College
admissions if at all yeah I mean I can
tell you on the on the screening of
application side it's not or at least it
hasn't yet if you submit an application
that is being reviewed by an actual
human person um they're not going to say
you know we had our AI read your essay
and you know welcome to the school or
you you know you can't come here you
forgot four commas and we detected it
yeah exactly uh that's not going to
happen um there are initiatives within
the
[Music]
schools it's a competing process right
because in a lot of ways they go like we
kind of want to squash AI because it's
an opportunity or a vehicle potentially
for cheating but then now you're having
a movement of of graduates saying we
aren't
prepared for the
workplace because we weren't trained in
AI we weren't taught anything about AI
so there's sort of a competing thing of
you know let's get more classes in AI
let's get more training and
understanding in AI because it's not
going anywhere um and also controlling
it because it does allow for it does
allow for people to cheat
um as far as my perspective with it I
have nothing against AI I think AI is a
useful tool um
if you use it properly I have had I'll
say two or three situations in which I
am working with a student on an essay
whether that's a college essay or you
know an essay for class and I'm going
okay so here are some of the edits you
need to make right you know maybe we
need to sharpen up this paragraph I
really like what you said here but you
know we've got to kind of like put these
things together and we'll sign off
that'll be the end of the session and
then they'll send me the work and you
know I'm seeing something that's like I
really want to go to the University of
Arizona because the University of
Arizona is a great School in the
southwest right and you're seeing this
whole thing and I'm
going and I don't want to accuse anybody
so I kind go you know I think that these
edits are maybe a little bit too basic
for you uh I think we could clean it up
I think we could get more of you into
this if I'm being perfectly honest reads
a little bit like AI wrote this nice
yeah let's get more specific with it
right so I can kind of throw that like
backand like you know I think you may
have done a right without openly
accusing somebody um but it is it is an
interesting thing because it's not it's
not going anywhere right and it's only
gon to get better and better and better
um but I think colleges are kind of
famously behind the curve on a lot of
things just because they're large
institutions that are kind of steeped in
process and
tradition yeah you know and like the top
universities you're talking about going
back to the 17th century these are not
these are not organizations that move
quickly with policy or make decisions um
expeditiously I'll say yeah yeah gotcha
yeah I mean yeah it's really cool to
think it's changing so quick and um uh
you know for us to see how it's useful
and you know not of benefit uh to us to
to use these to use these tools cuz
that's what they are you know it's not
going to solve all of our problems but
you know as we learn more and more about
it people spend more and more time with
it we we can uh you know be more of a
cyborg with our with our with our tools
that are that are changing and as as
chat GPT evolves um Matt I want to ask
you I wanted to back up a little bit man
I would love to know on the personal
side of things um I was listening to you
on another podcast I think that you said
is it true that you were a professional
hockey player is that correct
uh no I was never a professional hockey
player uh no okay you played hockey I
played hockey uh for most of my life I
was a very high Lev hockey player uh but
ultimately being a professional wasn't
in the cards for me um okay and it goes
back to the question you know when my gu
at Scout SL asked me like what would you
do if you didn't have to uh you know if
you didn't have to worry about money I
think my answer was probably like yeah
I'll play hockey and then play hockey
yeah yeah exactly I'll play hockey and
then you go like well great what happens
if you're not good enough and you go
well I'll um I don't know I'm 17 I
haven't thought about that yeah yeah
yeah terrifying okay yeah well okay so
um you know rewinding time back to when
you were 17 playing hockey and and you
were getting to the self I guess I would
just like to know how what was your
journey into being you
know your your life as a teen um you you
playing hockey into being a a mentor or
a a tutor and then um I mean now you you
guys have this this organization this um
you know these are these other people
that you work with um you're the founder
um is it mrm education that's you guys
mrm education and Elite tutoring so yeah
you founded this and You' you've
gathered these people who have these
other skills and now you're helping all
these all these people um all the all
these younger people how did you get to
there I mean what's what's the jump from
you as you're young you started
mentoring and tutoring at at at what age
and then how did it kind of lead into
what it is
now uh yeah it's a it's a great question
I mean I was that 17-year-old who was
like you know I don't necessarily know
what I want to do I knew I liked certain
things but ultimately like I said my
whole life was like I'm gonna go play
hockey uh right and then there's a
reality check of like I'm not going to
be able to do that so I got into writing
um politics government loved all that
type of stuff and ultimately the first
opportunity that presented itself when I
got out of college was to work with uh
you know one-on-one with students I was
working as an ESL teacher I was working
as a private tutor um and so that kind
of led me down this path ultimately the
reason that I got into um like starting
my own company was I realized a trend
that exists within both College Prep
tutoring SAT prep all of that stuff uh
in
that tutoring can be a very expensive
service there are tutors that charge you
know $250 $300 an hour companies that
charge that and the belief is at least
on the parent side that well I'm paying
$200 an hour for my tutor they must be
excellent um and the reality is they
might be excellent because those
tutoring companies are still only paying
their tutors 25 $35 an hour so
ultimately what you get is a lot of like
myself 22 23 year olds who are out of
college so maybe I'm good maybe I'm not
good right you get a lot of people who
are in grad school working to become a
doctor or a lawyer you get a lot of
people who are uh scratching out a
living as a Creator or an artist or a
writer and they're using what they
learned in college to kind of teach
these people um and I thought you know
this is crazy that these families are
paying $200 $250 an hour and they're
getting a tutor that can't really be
that flexible with their schedule
because they're doing something else or
a tutor that is eventually going to be
like you know this was fun but like I'm
going to to go be a doctor now right um
and ultimately a tutor that is a
part-time person right and so I thought
I thought this is this is crazy we can't
do this anymore so I started my company
with the understanding that we would
professionalize the process we were
going to pay a significantly higher wage
we start our tutors at $80 an hour now
um and the idea being that they won't
need to pack their schedule with eight
students a day to make ends meet uh they
will be uh incentivized to be able to
reschedule sessions to be able to be
flexible with their scheduling um and
that ultimately we wouldn't I would be
able to weed out people who weren't
quite so good um so now I'm able to kind
of solve for like what I was saying
before with the like highly charismatic
people I'm able to get people who are
younger I'm able to get people who are
um interesting and relatable to talk to
which is actually probably the most
difficult thing for hiring I'm able to
hire people people who have um AP reader
experience which for those people who
aren't familiar with what that is they
are the graders of the AP test um so you
know you're talking about like high
level Educators we have college
professors we have um high school
department chairs uh and ultimately that
was kind of the idea is to say if you're
going to Shell out all this money for
tutoring you really ought to be getting
the service that you deserve to get and
if you're a tutor and you have all these
expertise and qualifications then you
ought to be getting the wage that you
deserve to get otherwise we're going to
constantly be in this system where
people are frustrated with the service
and they don't know why because
sometimes they can get a good tutor but
other times they can't get a good tutor
and they're like why why why is this
working sometimes but not other times
and you're realizing it's just kind of
like a luck of the draw situation right
right right yeah yeah yeah I get that
okay yeah that that's good um okay and
then so so how did you how did you start
rounding up people who who know I mean I
I assume there's other people that that
work for you I mean how did you stumble
across these people I'm sure they've got
pretty good resumes themselves uh yeah
well you know what it was it was it was
really easy when I put uh $80 an hour on
the uh on the on the job job posting um
and I started to get people who I was
interviewing I interviewed one woman who
was the um she was the mathematics
department chair at Southern New
Hampshire University
and she's talking about how she was a
biostatistician by trade and I'm
interviewing this woman thinking like
you are more qualified to be hiring me
than I am to be talk about impostor
syndrome yeah seriously right I'm going
like what what am I interviewing you for
um but you meet a lot of people like
that right and and I think ultimately
when it comes to being like a business
owner and and trying to be a responsible
business owner is that like people want
people want a couple things one they
want to feel like they're being
compensated properly for their expertise
and their time and two they want to feel
like they're part of something and I
think that's what we create when we say
like we're really trying to deliver that
service um so my process looks like you
know putting a job post out there
whether it's on LinkedIn or kind of word
of mouth uh and then meeting people
because if you can be relatable and you
can be interesting and you can be
enjoyable then I have something for you
whereas I don't care how many degrees
you have or what you know what your
expertise is if you aren't interesting
and enjoyable to talk to if I can't
connect with you if someone can't
connect with you then ultimately they're
just going to continue to struggle with
whatever they were struggling with
before they came to you you
know yeah yeah it's it's more than just
what's on the paper you know like you
don't just all right I have these
accomplishments now I just sit here and
everything good happens you know D it'd
be like having a podcast guests who knew
everything about you know I I don't know
but they you know were unable to to
speak or or have a conversation you know
yeah yeah yeah they can be brilliant but
I mean yeah I mean Charisma go goes a
long way and and something I learn you
know about myself and other people is uh
you know certain areas I can be car
charismatic certain subjects I can be
incredibly charismatic there's things
that I am so passionate about that other
people might not care about at all but
you know get me talking about those
things and I'm going to come across
incredibly charismatic and interesting
and I might get you to be interested in
those things CU I'm so pumped about them
you know and so yeah just find finding
finding exactly where people fit and
giving them a little bit of space to you
know dance around I suppose I love that
I might be able to get you interested in
something you didn't care about like
describe to me the teaching tutoring
process in one sentence I might be able
to get you to care something to care
about something you didn't care about
before like that's beautiful yeah yeah
yeah super cool man well um yeah um okay
so so how long have you guys been in
business how long has your company been
around uh we've been around basically
from the pandemic we're fully virtual
um so that was kind of my opportunity to
say Hey you know like I can go I can do
this now right I don't need like a brick
and mortar location so yeah we've been
around since uh yeah mid
2020 okay and within those within those
years I mean what is a this a trick
question I suppose but what have you
learned what what what has it taught you
about yourself I mean this is a I'm sure
it's a lot of self-development by you
know being an entrepreneur starting a
company learning all these things what
have you learned about you or I guess
just about the whole thing in general
business is hard business is business is
hard you know I got into this and I was
an educator and I I knew going in that I
didn't know all these things about
business and so that was going to be
difficult um but the grind of being an
entrepreneur day in day out managing
people doing the same things over again
I mean we we were talking a little bit
about what we do in the summer for you
know an education company where we have
you know less clients um and just kind
of like keeping yourself self
disciplined and
and and staying on top of the things
when you don't have a boss breathing
down your neck it's wonderful in a lot
of ways because you do have that freedom
but then you know if you have the
freedom to prosper you also have the
freedom to fail um but I think the one
thing that I would say if I had to say I
would I took something away is that like
if you can be connected to the
why it really changes the game because
then you you do want to stay that you
know it's like every time I bring a new
tutor in or I you know make a connection
with a partner we partner with a company
or I go to a
fundraiser I see all these people and
I'm like you know I want to get that
tutor I want to get that tutor work I
want to I want to do that I go to the
fundraiser and I go like I want to help
these moms who are you know worried
about their kids with disabilities um
you so you know I want to I want to
offer value to that partner and and
being able to connect to that
why I think that's the that's the key if
you're Mission driven if you have a
purpose as to why you're doing it it all
becomes a lot easier yeah wow what a
beautiful answer I love that man yeah
it's cool I I feel like um you know it's
a everybody always talks about service
you know if you can like just pick
something that's bigger than you and so
we don't have to think it's so easy to
think about ourselves all the time right
you know so if you can have something
where you can be in a room and go that
person was interesting I I think I could
actually help them and then be able to
have the tools and resources to do so I
mean how cool is that you know like yeah
yeah yeah I I always quote this I always
find a way to jam it in there but uh uh
Romos he's a spiritual teacher he always
says we're all just walking each other
home you know I just I just feel like
what that means to me a lot of times is
you know I might have something that is
is useful for somebody else to like
Express themselves and and um you know
walk them towards their home as I'm
walking towards mine you know we're on
the same path so to say um well cool man
we are we are getting up here in time um
I I want to make sure that uh that we
covered everything that um that's
important for you I mean I want to make
sure everybody knows I'll include
everything in the description down below
everybody will have those links um is is
there anything else that people need to
know about mrm education Elite tutoring
anything no I think we we covered
everything in more brilliant brilliant
well I I love it man um I I'm hoping
some some people reach out to you from
this and um I man it was really nice
talking to you it was really cool to get
some of your perspective on this so I
really appreciate you reaching out and
then you know one more time again it's
really really grateful that you were
willing to reschedule you know I know I
did cancel on your last minute and
that's not not the most professional uh
business move there but I really
appreciate that man happens to the best
of this uh yeah this was a pleasure not
all podcasts are great and like
enjoyable to be on so like thank you for
having me and thanks for like making
this cool conversation this was fun yeah
yeah wonderful man all right well we'll
be in touch man um I'll send you I'll
send you a text um I'll get edit in all
this uh listeners love yourself if you
haven't drank any water today what are
you doing dude drink some water uh
stretch move around and then check out
the links below and check out Matt stuff
um if if you have any questions I'm sure
you could probably send over an email
and and he seems like he'd be pretty
happy to answer for you so everybody
have a good rest of your day Matt you as
well I'll be in touch thanks again
man thanks Jacob cheers all right see
you
man hello and welcome to the junkyard
love podcast
[Music]
at what age do we learn how to have
better
conversations at what age do we learn to
have better conversations with ourselves
[Music]
knowledge is
power reality is
[Music]